[{"question": "\u0427\u0442\u043e \u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0435 Python?", "options": ["\u042f\u0437\u044b\u043a \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0433\u0440\u0430\u043c\u043c\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u0438\u044f", "\u0422\u0438\u043f \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445", "\u041c\u0443\u0437\u044b\u043a\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u0438\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442", "\u0417\u043c\u0435\u044f \u043d\u0430 \u0430\u043d\u0433\u043b\u0438\u0439\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043c"], "correct_option": 0}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u0442\u0438\u043f \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0438\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0446\u0435\u043b\u044b\u0445 \u0447\u0438\u0441\u0435\u043b?", "options": ["int", "float", "str", "natural"], "correct_option": 0}, {"question": "\u0412 \u043a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043c \u0433\u043e\u0434\u0443 \u043d\u0430\u0447\u0430\u043b\u0430\u0441\u044c \u0412\u0442\u043e\u0440\u0430\u044f \u041c\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u044f \u0432\u043e\u0439\u043d\u0430?", "options": ["1923", "1934", "1941", "1938"], "correct_option": 2}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a \u043d\u0430\u0437\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0441\u0442\u043e\u043b\u0438\u0446\u0430 \u041d\u0438\u0434\u0435\u0440\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0434\u0438\u0438?", "options": ["\u041f\u0435\u043a\u0438\u043d", "\u0410\u043c\u0441\u0442\u0435\u0440\u0434\u0430\u043c", "\u0412\u0430\u0442\u0438\u043a\u0430\u043d", "\u0411\u0443\u0445\u0430\u0440\u0435\u0441\u0442"], "correct_option": 1}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0435 \u0441\u0430\u043c\u043e\u0435 \u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u043e\u0435 \u0436\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0435 \u0432 \u043c\u0438\u0440\u0435?", "options": ["\u0421\u043b\u043e\u043d", "\u0411\u0435\u043b\u0430\u044f \u0430\u043a\u0443\u043b\u0430", "\u0413\u0438\u043f\u043f\u043e\u043f\u043e\u0442\u0430\u043c", "\u0421\u0438\u043d\u0438\u0439 \u043a\u0438\u0442"], "correct_option": 3}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0435 \u0436\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0435 \u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0441\u0430\u043c\u044b\u043c \u0431\u044b\u0441\u0442\u0440\u044b\u043c \u0432 \u043c\u0438\u0440\u0435?", "options": ["\u0413\u0430\u0437\u0435\u043b\u044c", "\u0422\u0438\u0433\u0440", "\u041b\u0435\u043e\u043f\u0430\u0440\u0434", "\u0413\u0435\u043f\u0430\u0440\u0434"], "correct_option": 3}, {"question": "\u0421\u043a\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e \u043d\u043e\u0433 \u0443 \u043f\u0430\u0443\u043a\u043e\u0432?", "options": ["6", "4", "8", "12"], "correct_option": 2}, {"question": "\u041a\u0442\u043e \u043d\u0430\u043f\u0438\u0441\u0430\u043b \"\u0412\u043e\u0439\u043d\u0430 \u0438 \u043c\u0438\u0440\"?", "options": ["\u041b.\u0422\u043e\u043b\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439", "\u0418\u0432\u0430\u043d \u0445\u0443\u0434\u043e\u0439", "\u0410\u043b\u0435\u043a\u0441\u0430\u043d\u0434\u0440 \u041f\u0443\u0448\u043a\u0438\u043d", "\u0421\u0435\u0440\u0433\u0435\u0439 \u0415\u0441\u0435\u043d\u0438\u043d"], "correct_option": 0}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u0430 \u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c \u0441\u0432\u0435\u0442\u0430?", "options": ["100\u0442.\u043a\u043c/\u0441", "300\u0442.\u043a\u043c/\u0441", "\u0431\u0435\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0435\u0447\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c", "10\u0442.\u043a\u043c/\u0441"], "correct_option": 1}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u0433\u0440\u0438\u0431 \u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u044f\u0434\u043e\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044b\u043c?", "options": ["\u041e\u043f\u044f\u0442\u0430", "\u0420\u0435\u0431\u044f\u0442\u0430", "\u0413\u0440\u0443\u0437\u0434\u0438", "\u041c\u0443\u0445\u043e\u043c\u043e\u0440"], "correct_option": 3}]